Guide to the Reynolds Price Papers, 1880-2014 RL.01050
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Reynolds Price papers
1880-2014 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Price, Reynolds, 1933-2011
RL.01050
151 Linear Feet
1 Gigabytes 1,300 document (MS Word and text formats) and digital image files; approximately 1 gigabytes.
354 boxes
Reynolds Price (1933-2011) was a novelist, short story writer, poet, dramatist, essayist, translator, and James B. Duke Professor of English at Duke University, where he taught creative writing and literature beginning in 1958. He was an alumnus of Duke and of Oxford University, which he attended on a Rhodes Scholarship. He received fellowships from the Guggenheim Foundation and the National Endowment for the Arts, and his books were nominated for the Pulitzer Prize and the National Book Award. The collection is comprised of correspondence, writings, serials, clippings, speeches, interviews, legal and financial papers, photographs, audiovisual materials, and digital materials reflecting Price's career and personal life. Personal and professional correspondence document his education at Duke University, especially his studies under William Blackburn; his period abroad as a Rhodes Scholar at Merton College, Oxford; and his literary work and interaction with other authors, including Stephen Spender, Eudora Welty, and Allan Gurganus. Writings include manuscripts, typescripts, proofs, outlines, and notes produced in the creation and publication of all his major works, including: A Long and Happy Life; Kate Vaiden; A Palpable God; Clear Pictures; A Whole New Life; The Collected Stories; The Collected Poems; A Letter to a Godchild; Ardent Spirits; The Good Priest's Son, and many other books, individual stories, poems, and essays.
Scope and Contents
The (1) Correspondence Series is divided into the Correspondence, chronological subseries and the Correspondence, alphabetical by name subseries. The chronological correspondence subseries consists of letters to and from family, friends, teachers, and admirers of Price's work. The alphabetical correspondence subseries comprises correspondence between Price and other writers, literary figures, celebrities, and close friends including Eudora Welty and Stephen Spender. The (2) Writings Series contains various writings by Price and is divided into the Books, Scribner's Files, Uncollected Fiction and Nonfiction, Price Writing in Serials, Reviews by Price, Addresses and Speeches, and Audiovisual Recordings of Price Regarding Writing subseries. The Books subseries is composed chiefly of drafts, typescripts, and proofs of Price's novels, plays, autobiographical works, and volumes of poetry.
The (3) Events Series contains materials documenting Price's achievements, his education, and performances of his dramatic work and his speaking engagements, as well as performances, and presentations of interest to Price. The (4) Personal Papers Series has expanded significantly following the author's death. The Series contains many of the books, letters, art and photographs kept in his home, including personal health and financial records. The Series also includes personal scrapbooks, his postcard collection, and a collection of family home movies. Price's teaching career in the Duke University English Department is documented by the (5) Duke University Series. And manuscripts sent to Price by fellow authors and students make up the (6) Writings by Others Series.
Biographical / Historical
Chronology List
Chronology List
1933 Feb. 1 Born in Macon, NC, to William Solomon and Elizabeth (Rodwell) Price
1954-1955 Editor, The Archive; Advisory editor, Shenandoah at Duke University
1955 A.B. Summa cum laude, Duke University; Angier Duke Scholar
1958 D. Litt., St. Andrew's Presbyterian College B. Litt. (Rhodes Scholar), Merton College, Oxford University
1958 Member of English Department faculty, Duke University
1961-1968 Assistant Professor, Duke University
1962 A Long and Happy Life, first novel and book
1965 Writer-in-residence, University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill
1967, 1969 Writer-in-residence, University of Kansas
1968-1972 Associate professor, Duke University
1971 Writer-in-residence, University of North Carolina at Greensboro Glasgow Professor, Washington and Lee University
1972-1977 Professor, Duke University
1973-1977 Literature Advisory Panel, National Endowment for the Arts (Chair, 1976)
1977 Faculty, Salzburg Seminar
1977- James B. Duke Professor of English, Duke University
1979 National Book Award nomination for translation, for A Palpable God
1986 National Book Critics Circle Award for Fiction, for Kate Vaiden
1994 Finalist for Pulitzer Prize in fiction, for The Collected Stories
1997 The Collected Poems
2011 Jan. 20 Died following a heart attack, Durham, NC
Conditions Governing Access
RESTRICTED: Access to, and duplication by any means, of most materials in the Reynolds Price papers requires written permission from his literary executor. Prior consultation with the Associate Curator of Collections is required before permission can be granted. Please contact Research Services.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. There may be a 48-hour delay in obtaining these materials.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Related Materials
Materials related to the life and career of Reynolds Price appear in several other collections housed at the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library. The Clear Pictures Film Footage Collection houses materials created and used by Charles Guggenheim in making his 1994 documentary film about Price's life (based on Price's own 1989 memoir of the same title). The collection includes many materials that do not appear in the published version of the film: research, film footage of interviews of and about Price, and electronic files. Documentation of Price's professional writing career appears in the records of the Harriet Wasserman Literary Agency Records. Materials there include correspondence, drafts and published versions of his works, and publishing contracts both with this agency and with Russell and Volkening, Wasserman's employer prior to forming her own agency. Extensive documentation of Price's publishing history can be found in the Jody Jones Hunter Collection of Works by Reynolds Price. In addition to copies of Price's books with major commercial publishers, the Hunter collection also contains many small press publications, limited editions, periodicals, and audiovisual materials. Finally, the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library contains copies of many publications similar to those in the Hunter collection. These items, cataloged separately from the Reynolds Price Papers, are searchable by individual title in the Duke University Libraries online catalog.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Reynolds Price Papers were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift between 1986-2017.
Arrangement
Arrangement follows creator's chronological dates, where available. Archivist added versions where dates were unavailalbe.
Proofs (printed matter); Typescripts; Audiocassettes; Price family; College teachers -- North Carolina -- Correspondence; Poems; Videocassettes; Machine-readable records; Black-and-white photographs; Short stories -- 20th century; Speeches; Rhodes scholarships; Poets -- North Carolina; Literature -- History and criticism; Essays -- 20th century; Authors, American -- 20th century; American literature -- Southern States; Outlines (documents); Color photographs; Clippings (information artifacts); American literature -- 20th century; Authors, American -- 20th century -- Correspondence; Authors, American -- 20th century -- Diaries; Gay men -- Southern States; People with disabilities -- North Carolina -- Durham; Galley proofs; Authors and publishers -- United States; Manuscripts, American -- United States; Autograph albums; Playbills; Playwriting -- Drama; Caucasian race in literature; Duke University. Department of English; Blackburn, William, 1899-1972; Gurganus, Allan, 1947-; Welty, Eudora, 1909-2001; Duke University -- Faculty; Price, Reynolds, 1933-2011; Spender, Stephen, 1909-; Merton College; University of Oxford
- Correspondence, 1936-2014, undated
  Scope and Contents
  The Correspondence Series is divided into the Correspondence, chronological subseries and the Correspondence, alphabetical by name subseries. Materials arrived in different accessions and original divisions have been retained. The subseries includes multiple runs of general correspondence arranged in a loose chronological order. The chronological correspondence consists of letters to and from family, friends, teachers, and admirers of his work. Early letters vividly depict his relationships with family members and friends. Many of the letters dated between 1954 and 1958 concern his education at Duke University and as a Rhodes Scholar at Merton College, Oxford University. His early development as an author is documented here as well as in the Writings Series. From 1961 onward, letters also provide information about his career as a professor at Duke University. The alphabetical correspondence subseries comprises correspondence between Price and other writers, literary figures, celebrities, and close friends. These letters concern both personal and literary matters. Frequently the correspondents commented on each other's recent publications or on work in progress. Numerous letters to and from Eudora Welty and Stephen Spender reveal much about their strong influence on Price's development as a writer. The series also contains a great many letters from Allan Gurganus; Polly Holliday; Jeff Humphries; Josephine Humphreys; Wallace Kaufman; Joe Porter; Lee Smith; and William Blackburn.
  Conditions Governing Access
  RESTRICTED: Access to, and duplication by any means, of most materials in the Reynolds Price papers requires written permission from his literary executor. Prior consultation with the Associate Curator of Collections is required before permission can be granted. Please contact Research Services.
  Access to original electronic and audiovisual materials is restricted. Contact Research Services in advance to request the production of a use copy.
  - Correspondence, chronological, 1936-2011, undated
    This subseries includes correspondence between Price and family; friends; associates; students; and, business contacts, and is arranged chronologically.
    - Correspondence, 1936-1955 Oct; 12 folders (Box 1)
    - Correspondence, 1955 Nov-1956 Dec; 15 folders (Box 2)
    - Correspondence, 1957 Jan-1958 Jun; 12 folders (Box 3)
    - Correspondence, 1958 Jul-1960 Dec; 11 folders (Box 4)
    - Correspondence, 1961 Jan-1963 Sep; 11 folders (Box 5)
    - Correspondence, 1963 Oct-1966 Mar; 11 folders (Box 6)
    - Correspondence, 1966 Apr-1968 Sep; 13 folders (Box 7)
    - Correspondence, 1968 May-1970 Feb; 13 folders (Box 8)
    - Correspondence, 1970 Mar-1971 Jun; 11 folders (Box 9)
    - Correspondence, 1971 Jul-1972 May; 10 folders (Box 10)
    - Correspondence, 1972 Jun-1973 Aug; 13 folders (Box 11)
    - Correspondence, 1973 Sep-1974 Oct; 12 folders (Box 12)
    - Correspondence, 1974 Nov-1976 Feb 13; 14 folders (Box 13)
    - Correspondence, 1976 Feb 16-1977 Mar; 12 folders (Box 14)
    - Correspondence, 1977 Apr-1978 May; 14 folders (Box 15)
    - Correspondence, 1978 Jun-1979 Oct; 16 folders (Box 16)
    - Correspondence, 1979 Nov-1981 Mar; 17 folders (Box 17)
    - Correspondence, 1981 Apr-1982 Jun; 15 folders (Box 18)
    - Correspondence, 1982 Jul-1983 Apr; 11 folders (Box 19)
    - Correspondence, 1983 May-1984 Jun 11; 14 folders (Box 20)
    - Correspondence, 1984 Jun 12-1985 Mar; 12 folders (Box 21)
    - Correspondence, 1985 Apr-1986 Aug; 17 folders (Box 22)
    - Correspondence, 1986 Sep-1987 May; 11 folders (Box 23)
    - Correspondence, 1987 Jun-1988 May; 12 folders (Box 24)
    - Correspondence, 1988 Jun-1989 May; 12 folders (Box 25)
    - Correspondence, 1989 Jun-1990 Feb; 12 folders (Box 26)
    - Correspondence, 1990 Mar-Nov; 12 folders (Box 27)
    - Correspondence, 1990 Dec-1991 Aug; 14 folders (Box 28)
    - Correspondence, 1991 Aug-1992 May; 13 folders (Box 29)
    - Correspondence, 1992 Jun- Dec, undated; 12 folders (Box 30)
    - Correspondence, 1992 Jan-Dec; 19 folders (Box 31)
    - Correspondence, 1993 Jan 3-Jun 15; 18 folders (Box 32)
    - Correspondence, 1993 Jun 16-circa 1993; 19 folders (Box 33)
    - Correspondence, 1994 Jan 1-Jun 22; 14 folders (Box 34)
    - Correspondence, 1994 Jun 28-Oct 9; 14 folders (Box 35)
    - Correspondence, 1994 Oct 10-1995 Jan 10; 13 folders (Box 36)
    - Correspondence, 1995 Jan 11-Apr 19; 13 folders (Box 37)
    - Correspondence, 1995 Apr 20-Jul 9; 11 folders (Box 38)
    - Correspondence, 1995 Jul 10-Sep 24; 11 folders (Box 39)
    - Correspondence, 1995 Sep 25-Dec 12; 11 folders (Box 40)
    - Correspondence, 1995 Dec 13-1996 Feb 6; 10 folders (Box 41)
    - Correspondence, 1996 Feb 7-Apr 19; 9 folders (Box 42)
    - Correspondence, 1996 Apr 20-Jul 9; 10 folders (Box 43)
    - Correspondence, 1996 Jul 10-Oct 31; 9 folders (Box 44)
    - Correspondence, 1996 Nov 1-1997 Feb 28; 12 folders (Box 45)
    - Correspondence, 1997 Mar 3-Aug 22; 11 folders (Box 46)
    - Correspondence, 1997 Aug 24-Dec 31; 10 folders (Box 47)
    - Correspondence, 1998 Jan 1-Jul 31; 10 folders (Box 48)
    - Correspondence, 1998 Aug 1-Dec 31; 11 folders (Box 49)
    - Correspondence, 1999 Jan 1-Sep 30; 10 folders (Box 50)
    - Correspondence, 1999 Oct 1-2000 Apr 28; 9 folders (Box 51)
    - Correspondence, 2000 May-2001 Jan; 10 folders (Box 52)
    - Correspondence, 2001 Feb-2002 Mar; 15 folders (Box 53)
    - Correspondence, 2002 Apr-2003 May; 15 folders (Box 54)
    - Correspondence, 2003 Jun-2004 Jul; 15 folders (Box 55)
    - Correspondence, 2004 Aug-2005 Jul; 10 folders (Box 56)
    - Correspondence, 2005 Aug-2006 Nov; 9 folders (Box 57)
    - Correspondence, 2006 Dec-2007 Dec; 9 folders (Box 58)
    - Correspondence, 2008 Jan-2009 Mar; 8 folders (Box 203)
    - Correspondence, 2009 Apr-Dec; 9 folders (Box 204)
    - Correspondence, 2010-2011, undated; 7 folders (Box 205)
    - Correspondence, undated; 5 folders (Box 206)
    - Correspondence, undated; 3 folders (Box 207)
    - Unsorted correspondence, 1956-2010; 19 folders (Box 59)
      Includes oversized correspondence and associated attachments.
    - Unsorted correspondence, 1992-2000, undated; 10 folders (Box 338)
    - Electronic correspondence, 1984-2004, undated; 249 Files 249 MS Word files and emails, 4.8 MB (Digital-materials RL01050-SET-0001)
      Correspondence to publishers, Duke colleagues, and friends.
  - Correspondence, alphabetical by name, 1940-2014
    This subseries includes correspondence between Price and other writers, literary figures, celebrities, and close friends, and is arranged alphabetically by name.
    - Abbott, Shirley, 1986 (Box 60)
    - Adcock, Betty, 1996-2006, undated (Box 60)
    - Albee, Edward, 1963-1981, undated (Box 60)
    - American Academy of Arts and Letters, 1992-2001; 7 folders (Box 202)
    - American Academy of Arts and Letters, 2002-2014, undated; 7 folders (Box 68)
    - Anderson, Jeff, 1979 (Box 60)
    - Applewhite, Jim, 1970-1998 (Box 60)
    - Athas, Daphne, 1971-2002, undated (Box 60)
    - Auden, Wystan H., 1960, undated (Box 60)
    - Bayes, Ron, 1969-1985 (Box 60)
    - Bell, Madison Smartt, 1999-2000 (Box 60)
    - Betts, Doris, 1970-1990 (Box 60)
    - Bingham, Sallie, 1998-2007 (Box 60)
    - Blackburn, William and family, 1953-2006, undated; 2 folders (Box 60)
    - Blackburn, William and family, 1979 (Box 59)
    - Bly Robert, 1998 (Box 60)
    - Boatwright, James, 1960-1976, 1988; 6 folders (Box 60)
    - Brondoli, Michael, 1972-1986, undated (Box 60)
    - Brooks, Cleanth, 1964-1990 (Box 60)
    - Broughton, T. Alan, 1968-1991 (Box 60)
    - Broughton, T. Alan, 1972 (Box 59)
    - Brown, Lightning, 1995; 4 folders (Box 61)
    - Buechner, Frederick, 1969-2000 (Box 61)
    - Busch, Frederick, 1969-1991, undated (Box 61)
    - Carr, Virginia, 2002-2005 (Box 61)
    - Campbell, Alan, 1958-1962 (Box 61)
    - Cecil, David and family, 1956-1990, undated (Box 61)
    - Chappell, Fred, 1961-1990, undated (Box 61)
    - Clinton, William, 1998 (Box 61)
    - Coles, Robert, 1993-1994 (Box 61)
    - Conroy, Pat, 1989 (Box 61)
    - Corn, Alfred, 1988-1990 (Box 61)
    - Cowley, Malcolm, 1972-1975 (Box 61)
    - Cox, Elizabeth, 1979-2002 (Box 61)
    - Crews, Harry, 1971 (Box 61)
    - Davidson, Cathy, 1994-1999 (Box 62)
    - de Buys, William, 1993-1994 (Box 62)
    - Dickey, James, 1968-2001 (Box 62)
    - Dillard, Annie, 1995-1998, undated (Box 62)
    - Dort, Dorothy, 1956-1958 (Box 62)
    - Douglas, Ellen (Josephine Harton), 1981-1982 (Box 62)
    - Edgerton, Clyde, 1990-1999 (Box 62)
    - Ellison, Ralph, 1964-1974 (Box 62)
    - Farrar, Geraldine, 1950-1951 (Box 62)
    - Fellowship of Southern Writers, 2006 (Box 62)
    - Foote, Horton, 1984-2002, undated (Box 62)
    - Ford, Richard, 1995-2003 (Box 62)
    - Fort, Charles, 1992-1993 (Box 62)
    - Franklin, John Hope, 1994 (Box 62)
    - Gibbons, Kaye, 1989-1999, undated (Box 62)
    - Gilchrist, Ellen, 1978-1997 (Box 62)
    - Grimsley, Jim, 1999 (Box 62)
    - Gordimer, Nadine, 1999 (Box 62)
    - Gurganus, Allan, 1974-2002, undated; 4 folders (Box 62)
    - Gurganus, Allan, undated (Box 59)
    - Guy, David, 1971-2002 (Box 62)
    - Hannah, Barry, 1987 (Box 226)
    - Harrison, Jim, 1973-2005 (Box 226)
    - Haydn, Hiram, 1958-1973 (Box 226)
    - Hays, Tommy 1999-2002 (Box 226)
    - Henley, Beth, 1988-1990 (Box 226)
    - Henley, Beth, 1989 (Box 59)
    - Holliday, Polly, 2004-2010 (Box 226)
    - Humphries, Jeff, 1977-1997; 2 folders (Box 226)
    - Humphreys, Josephine, 1967-2002, undated; 2 folders (Box 226)
    - Humphreys, Josephine, 1984 (Box 226)
    - Isherwood, Christopher, 1977 (Box 226)
    - Jakubs, Deborah, 2005-2008 (Box 226)
    - James, Sonja, 2003-2010 (Box 226)
    - Jordan, Michael, 2004, 2008 (Box 226)
    - Kaufman, Wallace, 1958-2007, undated; 7 folders (Box 63)
    - Kimmel, Haven, 2001 (Box 63)
    - Kizer, Carolyn, 1972-1994, undated (Box 63)
    - Kizer, Carolyn, 1973 (Box 59)
    - Knowles, John, 1963-1969; 2 folders (Box 63)
    - Kramer, Larry, 1999-2000 (Box 63)
    - Kreyling, Michael, 1978-2006, undated (Box 63)
    - Kushner, Tony, 1999 (Box 63)
    - Lee, Harper, 2007 (Box 63)
    - Leigh, Viven (her secretary), 1950 Jul (Box 63)
    - Levertov, Denise, 1972 (Box 63)
    - Linney, Romulus, 1965-2003, undated; 2 folders (Box 64A)
    - MacLeish, Roderick, 1994 (Box 64A)
    - Mailer, Norman, 1977, 1984 (Box 64A)
    - Malone, Michael, 2000, undated (Box 64A)
    - Malouf, Melissa, 2003 (Box 64A)
    - Maron, Margaret, 1994 (Box 64A)
    - Massengill, William, 2001-2004 (Box 64A)
    - Maxwell, William, 1997-2000 (Box 64A)
    - McFee, Michael, 1993-1994 (Box 64A)
    - Meredith, William, 1970-1979 (Box 64A)
    - Mitchell, Julian, 1959-1988, undated (Box 64A)
    - Moldow, Susan, 2002-2010 (Box 64A)
    - Morgan, Robert, 2000-2003, undated (Box 64A)
    - Morgenthau, Jr., Henry, 1944 May 9 (Box 64A)
      Includes the signature of the Secretary of the Treasury for Price's autograph collection.
    - Morris, Willie, 1997 (Box 64B)
    - Morrison, Toni, 1974-1992, undated (Box 64B)
    - Naumoff, Lawrence, 1972-2000 (Box 64B)
    - Nelson, Betty Palmer, 1992 (Box 64B)
    - Oates, Joyce Carol, 1976-1983 (Box 64B)
    - O'Brien, Edna, 1962 (Box 64B)
    - Orphanos, Stathis, 1986 (Box 64B)
      Includes printed note from Stathis and his photography of nudes.
    - Owen, Guy, 1974-1976 (Box 64B)
    - Parker, Dorothy, 1961 (Box 64B)
    - Patton, Frances Gray, 1960-1977 (Box 64B)
    - Payne, Peggy, 1994 (Box 64B)
    - Peacock, Phyliss, 1950, 1952, undated (Box 64B)
    - Pearson, T. R., 1986 (Box 64B)
    - Pełczyński, Zbigniew, 2009 (Box 64B)
    - Percy, Walker, 1966-1992 (Box 64B)
    - Porter, Joe, 1980-2006 (Box 64B)
    - Price, Leontyne, 1975-1983, 1995, undated (Box 64B)
    - Price, Mary Elizabeth (Memsy), 2007, 2009 (Box 64B)
    - Price, William, 2001-2008 (Box 64B)
    - Ransom, John Crowe, 1987 (Box 64B)
    - Rorem, Ned, 1997-2005 (Box 64B)
    - Rubin, Louis, 1965-1997 (Box 64B)
    - Salinger, Wendy, 1997-2005 (Box 64B)
    - Salmen, Chas, 2005 (Box 64B)
      Includes Live RFM Coverage of the Trial of Raphael vs. The State of Heaven.
    - Schiff, James, 1994-2002 (Box 64B)
    - 1990, 1996-2009 (Box 65)
      Includes correspondence from Nan Graham and Susan Muldow.
    - Seay, Jim, 1973-1990 (Box 65)
    - Sendak, Maurice, 1999 (Box 65)
    - Settle, Mary Lee, 1978-1982 (Box 65)
    - Settle, Mary Lee, 1979 (Box 59)
    - Shivers, Louise, 1976-1986, undated (Box 65)
    - Smith, Charlie, 1969-1989, undated; 2 folders (Box 65)
    - Smith, Dave, 1988-2000, undated; 2 folders (Box 65)
    - Smith, Lee, 1969-2003 (Box 65)
    - Smith, Moody, 1995-2010 (Box 65)
    - Snyder, Gary, 1974-1977 (Box 65)
    - Sondheim, Stephen, 1997 (Box 65)
    - Spencer, Elizabeth, 1987-2002 (Box 65)
    - Spender, Stephen, 1956-1961 Sep; 9 folders (Box 65)
      See also Stephen Spender correspondence in the Personal Papers Series.
    - Spender, Stephen, 1961 Oct -1999, undated; 5 folders (Box 66)
    - Steele, Max, 1967-1988, undated (Box 66)
    - Steele, Max, 1975 (Box 59)
    - Styron, William, 1956-1994 (Box 66)
    - Tan, Amy, 1995 (Box 66)
    - Tate, Allen, 1966-1975 (Box 66)
    - Taylor, James, 2001 (Box 66)
    - Tyler, Anne, 1960-2003, 2008, undated (Box 66)
    - Updike, John, 1962-2000, undated (Box 66)
    - Verdelle, A. J., 1996 (Box 66)
    - Voll, Daniel, 1984-2001, undated (Box 66)
      Manuscripts removed to Writing by Others Series.
    - Vonnegut, Kurt, 1997 (Box 66)
    - Wallace, Randall, 1971-1986 (Box 66)
    - Warren, Robert Penn, 1980 (Box 66)
    - Wasserman, Harriet, 1986, 2003-2007 (Box 66)
    - Waters, Ethel, 1950 (Box 66)
      Includes a signed photographs of Ethel Waters.
    - Welty, Eudora, 1969-1983, 1985-1989, 2006; 2 folders (Box 59)
    - Welty, Eudora and Eudora Welty Foundation, 1940-1994, 2002-2010, undated; 9 folders (Box 67)
    - Williams, Jonathan, 1969-1984 (Box 67)
    - Williams, Jonathan, 1977-1978 (Box 59)
    - Electronic correspondence, 1999-2004, undated; 2.6 Megabytes 105 MS Word documents and text files, 2.6 MB (Digital-materials RL01050-SET-0001)
      Includes Price correspondence with Richard Brodhead; Allan Gruganus; Polly Holliday; Memsy Price, Charlie Rose; Scribner; Moody Smith; Anne Tyler; John Updike; Daniel Voll; Kurt Vonnegut; Harriet Wasserman; and Eudora Welty.
- Writings, 1946-2014, undated